<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Salvage Auction India</string>
    <string name="auction">Auction</string>
    <string name="final_">Final</string>
    <string name="spare">Spare</string>
    <string name="fresh">Fresh</string>
    <string name="bank_seized">Bank Seized</string>
    <string name="vehicle">Vehicles</string>
    <string name="part">Parts</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="sell">Sell Car</string>
    <string name="my_ads">My Ads</string>
    <string name="rupee">&#x20B9;</string>
    <string name="missing_belongings">As Per Photos 1 Key, Tool Kit, Spare Wheel, Battery and VIP Number will be Retained by the Owner</string>
    <string name="note">These are insurance claimed salvage vehicles sold in as is where is condition</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions">1) Inspect vehicles before bidding.\n\n
2) Interested buyers are requested to physically inspect the salvage vehicles prior to final.\n\n
3) No guarantee on cheap parts and major parts.\n\n
4) No guarantee on extra damage .\n\n
5) If battery, Stepney, tool kit , jack wheel music system will present in workshop you will get other wise is missing.\n\n
6) Extra fitted accessories will be removed by insured.\n\n
7) Please see the vehicle physically and bid accordingly.\n\n
8) The buyer should be ready to lift the vehicle .\n\n
9) Before placing the quotes/ bids the buyer has to definitely make arrangements for physical inspection pictures attached are just for the referral purpose.\n\n
10) The extent of damage might not be know exactly through pictures.\n\n
11) May have the Rc or the insured might be applying for the duplicate Rc the detail are exactly not available buyers may bid accordingly.\n\n
12) Manufacture year details may be checked in transport or govt website .\n\n
13) DD needs to be submitted and salvage to be lifted within 5 days without fail.\n\n
14) Scan copy of DD and buyer affidavit needs to be shared with us before vehicle lifting.\n\n
15) Ownership to be transferred within 30 days from the date of lifting.\n\n
16) DD title has been shared on behalf of insured.\n\n
17) Buyer affidavit needs to be prepared on Rs. 100/- stamp papers duly notarized.\n\n
18) Salvage wil not be handed over if correct dd and buyer affidavit is submitted to concerned csm and date on affidavit should not be more than 3 days old.\n\n
19) the photos given are only indicative and you are requested to conduct physically inspection of the vehicle.\n\n
20) All quote will be considered as given for the vehicle is as is where is condition excluding extra accessories fitting.\n\n
21) Any additional information required please contact us before participating in auction.\n\n
22) Final confirmation of vehicle is subject to the consent of insured /consumer minimum approval time is 2 to 20 working days from the date of auction.\n\n
23) It is clearly advised to have a through physical inspection of the vehicle.\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="about_us">WelCome to salvage auction india.
India\'\s leading online salvage auction platform.\n\n
Here you can find Daily salvage auction of\n
Total loss Vehicles.\n
Weather Damage Vehicles.\n
Floods Loss vehicles.\n
Fire damage vehicles.\n
Theft recover vehicles.\n
Accidental vehicles etc.\n\n
with 90% approval rate in pan india please let us know how we can help you.
    </string>
</resources>